Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1915-2010, UWM Archival Collection 48; 19 cubic ft. (23 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - Poetry Society, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Policies and Regulations Governing Greek Houses and Lodges, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Polish Club, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Political Action and Arts Network, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 138)
  - Political Awareness Group Against Noninvolvement, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 139)
  - Political Items Collectors Klub, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Political Science Association, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pompon Girls, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Portrait of an Artist, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 140)
  - Positive Leadership Under Students, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 141)
  - Potomac Film Productions, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Pre-Teachers Organization at UWM, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 142)
  - Pre-Theological Club, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Pre-Veterinarian Club, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - Prem Kanta, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Press Club at UWM, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Prime Time Backgammon Club, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Prime Time for Women, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Prism, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  - Probe, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - ProBuColls, 1966-1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Professional and Academic League, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Professionals in Training, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - Progress Through Action, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 146)
  - Progressive Iranian Muslim Students, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Progressive List for Peace, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - Progressive Programmers, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 148)
  - Progressive Programmers of Wisconsin, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 149)
  - Progressive Student Forum, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Progressive Students Alliance, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Project Black
    - 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Project Concern, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Pro-Life at UWM, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 150)
  - Protest Literature, 1940, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Psi Chi, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Psi World Vanguard of Wisconsin, UWM Chapter, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Psychology Club at UWM, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 151)
  - Publications Committee
    - Accounts, 1925-1952 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
    - Minutes, 1933-1956 (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
  - Purin Hall Residents Association, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 152)
  - Purin Hall Tenants Union, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Pythagorean Club, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Que's, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Racquetball Club at UWM, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Radical Education Committee, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Ranger Rifle Club, 1957-1990 (Box 18, Folder 153)
  - Rap House, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Rationalist Church of America, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Ray Mendoza Defense Fund, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Reaganbusters, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Real Investment & Speculation Klub, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Recreational Facilities, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Reforms According to the Voice of Everyone (RAVE), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 154)
  - Refuse and Resist!, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 155)
  - Registered Nurse Association, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Relaxation Club, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 156)
  - Relevant Action Party, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Religious Studies Association at UWM, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Renaissance Art Guild, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Renegade Time Lords, 1983-1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Reorganized Latter Day Saint Student Centre, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The Representative, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Representative Party, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Representative Speakers Bureau, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Republican Unit, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Residence Hall Visitation Experiments, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Revolutionary Student Brigade, 1972-1977 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Riflemen at UWM, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Robert Kennedy Memorial, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Roger Faulkner for Senate, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Roscoe, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - ROTC Organizations, 1958-1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rowing Club, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Rush Booklets, 1957-1968 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Russ Feingold for U.S. Senate at UWM, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - S.O.R.A.L.E., 1976-1982 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Safewalk, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - St. Paul Christian Methodist Episcopal Mission, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Sammy Younge Brigade, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Sandburg Commons Advisory Board, 1986-1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Sandburg Hall, 1971-1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Sane Nuclear Policy Committee, 1958-1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - SARUP Soccer Club, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - SARUP Student Society, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Scabbard and Blade, 1958-1987 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Scholars for Mental Vacuity, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - School of Allied Health Professions Student Council, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - School of Education Club, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Schweitzer Club, 1961-1968 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Science Fiction Services, 1976-1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Science of Creation Club, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Scientific Debate Invitational, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - "Scoop" Pamphlets, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Screaming Eagle Arts, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Scuba Club, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Secondary Division, 1925-1960 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Secondary Education Club, 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Section .09(5) Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Segregated Fee Advisory Committee
    - 1969-1976 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Athletic Fees, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Minutes, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 57-58)
    - Procedures, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Self-Actualizing Student Association, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Semper Fidelis Society, 1977-1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Senior Class
    - 1915-1956 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 1958-1966 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Senior Classes, 1958-1973 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Seniors for a Meaningful Class Gift, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - S.H.A.P.E. (Students Helping Achieve Political Ethics), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Shepard Alumni House, 1945?-1961 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Shepherds, 1986-1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Shorts Film Society, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Sigma Alpha Eta, 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1964-1972 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Sigma Delta Omega, 1957-1961, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Sigma Delta Pi, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sigma Delta Psi, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Sigma Delta Sigma, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Sigma Epsilon Ksi, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Sigma Epsilon Sigma, 1964-1983 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Sigma Iota Lambda, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Sigma Kappa Alpha, 1950-1957 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Sigma Omicron Delta, 1954-1958 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Sigma Pi, 1964-1970 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Sigma Sigma Sigma
    - 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - 1957-1987 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Sigma Tau Delta, 1960-1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Sigma Tau Gamma, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Sigma XI, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Simply A Social Organization, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Sisters in Struggle, 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Six Fathom Club, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Slavic Club, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Slumber Party, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Smiths Fan Club, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Snide, Humor Magazine, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Snowboarders Club of UWM, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Social Action for Gender Equality, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Social Democratic Party, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Social Event Summaries, 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Social Psychology Coalition, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Social Work Club, 1957-1968 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Socialists, 1975-1987 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Society for a Better Society, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Society for Creative Anachronism, Inc., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Society for Ecological Enthusiasts, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Society for Formal Discussion, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Society for Study of Visual Anthropology, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Society for the Advancement of Future Minority Doctors, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Society for the Advancement of Management
    - 1957-1967 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - 1959-1973 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Financial Records, 1958-1963 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Society for the Investigation of Marxism, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Society of Engineers & Applied Scientists, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Society of Individualists, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Society of Professional Engineers, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Society of Professional Journalists, 1963-1993 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Society of Professional Journalists, 1965-1974 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Society of Student Engineers, 1947-1965 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Society of Typographic Arts, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Society of Urbanologists, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Society to Clothe Animals, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Sociocultural Research Center, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Socratic Society at UWM, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Song of the T'ai-chi T'u, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Sororities, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Sound Board, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Southeast Transit Research Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Spanish and Portuguese Club, 1958-1971 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Spanish Club, 1958-1964 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Spectrum, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Spinnakers Sailing Club, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Sport Parachute Club, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Sports Car Club
    - 1958-1967 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Spuds - A Daga - Epsilon, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Square One, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Stamp Out Petty Politics, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Standard Oil Teaching Awards, 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - S.T.A.R. (Students Taking an Active Role), 1994 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - States Rights Association, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stomp! Productions, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Stonerock Festival Concert, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Stop Waste in S.A., 1987 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Stowell House Association, 1957-1968 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Student Action Party, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Student Activities Caucus, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Student Advisory Committee for the Music Department, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Student Affiliates of the American Chemical Society
    - 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - 1968-1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Student Association
    - 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1-5)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Academic Policy, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Administrative, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Agendas, 2005-2007 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Committee Appointments
      - 1993-2008 (Box 22, Folder 12-26)
      - Academic Units, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
      - Administrative, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
      - Disciplinary, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
      - Faculty, 1993-2006 (Box 23, Folder 7-9)
    - Committee Requirements Documents, 1977-1993 (Box 23, Folder 10-12)
    - Committee Rosters, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Elections, 1957-1989 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Executive Committee, 1957-1990 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Faculty, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Financial Aid, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Master Committee List, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Information Packets, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991-2002 (Box 23, Folder 21-22)
    - Orientation
      - 1958-1989 (Box 23, Folder 23-47)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - Senate Meeting Summaries, 1994-2002 (Box 24, Folder 4-6)
    - Senate Minutes, 1991-2010 (Box 24, Folder 7-19)
    - Senate Reports, 1983-1987 (Box 24, Folder 20-23)
    - Social Welfare, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Student Activity Guide, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Student Court Actions, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - University General, 1981-1992 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Student Association for Research and Enlightenment, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Student Book Cooperative, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Student Club of the American Institute of Industrial Engineers, 1972-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Student Coalition Against Racism, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Student Coalition Group, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Student Committee for Landry, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Student Committee for UNICEF, 1989-1993 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Student Communication Association, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Student Concern on Relevant Engineering, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Student Coordinating Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Student Defense Coalition, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Student Disciplinary Guidelines, 1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Student Drinkers, Inc., 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Student Education Association, 1963-1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Student Equality Fellowship, 1963-1967 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Student-Faculty Committee To End The War In Vietnam, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Student Film Organization of Milwaukee, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Student Front, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Student Government
    - Constitutions and Registrations, 1957-1989 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Resolutions, 1957-1980 (Box 24, Folder 29-30)
    - Resolutions External to the University, 1959-1990 (Box 24, Folder 31-32)
  - Student Handbook, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Student Handicapped Affiliation for Recreational Enjoyment, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Student Housing Administration Council, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Student Leadership Awards, 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Student League for Improvement, 1971-1987 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Student Life and Interests Committee, 1965-1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Student Mobilization Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Student Movement for the Attainment of Consumer Knowledge, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Student Newspaper Survey, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Student Newspapers Report, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Student Nurse Organization, 1966-1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Student Nurses for the Awareness of Political Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Student Opportunity Society, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Student Organization for Athletic Grant-in-Aid, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Student Organization for Educational Diversity, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Student Organization Handbook, 1969-1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Student Organization Manual, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Student Organization Statistics, 1971-1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Student Pharmaceutical Society, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Student Polish Cultural Club, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Student Program Committee, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Student Purity Party, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Student Religious Liberals, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Student Research & Design Group, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Student Review at UWM, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Student Socialist Forum, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Student Society for the Study of Transpersonal Psychology, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Student Sociological Association, 1972-1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Student Speakers Bureau, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Student Strike, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Student Tax Association, 1986-1991 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Student Travel Club at UWM, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Student Tutorial Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Student Union, 1964-1972 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Student University Debate Society, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Student Voice, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Student Workers Organizing Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Student YWCA at UWM, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Student Zionist Organization, 1959-1967 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Students Against Monopolies on Campus, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Students Against Morally Bankrupt Senators, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Students Against University Racism, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Students Agreeing with Moody, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Students Aligned for Efficiency (SAFE), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Students Coalition of Promoting Equality (SCOPE), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Students for a Better UWM, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Students for a Color-Blind Campus, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 38-40)
  - Students for a Free Latvia, 1976-1988 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Students for a Free Market Economy, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Students for a Free Southern Africa, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Students for a Libertarian Society, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Students for a More Responsive School Board, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Students for a Peaceful Society, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Students for a United Ireland, 1981-1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Students for Autonomy, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Students for Barb Notestein, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Students for Baker, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Students for Bob Kasten, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Students for Braun for Congress, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Students for Bush
    - 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Students for Carpenter, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Students for Chvala, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Students for Child Care, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Students for Clinton/Gore, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Students for Consistency in Government, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Students for Conta, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Students for Cranston, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Students for Disarmament, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Students for Dole at UWM, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Students for Don Sykes, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Students for Donna Horowitz, 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Students for Dukakis, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Students for Earl, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Students for Economic Freedom at UWM, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Students for Eunice Edgar, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Students for Fred Kessler, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Students for Garvey, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Students for Gary Hart, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Students for George McGovern, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Students for Griffin, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Students for Habitat for Humanity International, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Students for Hall-Davis, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Students for Honesty at UWM, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Students for Jerry Schulz, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Students for Jim Moody, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Students for John Anderson, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Students for John Norquist (for Mayor), 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Students for Jordahl, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Students for Justice, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Students for Kasten, 1985-1992 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Students for Kemp, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Students for Kohl
    - 1988 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - 1994 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Students for Koneazny, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Students for Life, 1973-1986 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Students for Lindsay, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Students for Mass Communication, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Students for McGovern, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Students for Nelson, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Students for Nuclear Disarmament, 1978-1990 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Students for Origins Research, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Students for Palestine, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Students for Patricia A. Barnes, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Students for Peace and Justice in the Middle East, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Students for Personal Growth, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Students for Positive Change, 1978-1987 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Students for Progressive Education, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Students for Reagan, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Students for Reagan at UWM, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Students for Reagan/Bush, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Students for Recovery, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Students for Reform in Food Service, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Students for Representative Government, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Students for Safe Fire Arms Handling, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Students for Schreiber, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Students for Schulz, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Students for Spring Break, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Students for Stacy, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Students for Stokes, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Students for Stower, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Students for Student Drinkers, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Students for Student Government Reform, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Students for Student Travel at UWM, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Students for Students, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Students for Synthetic Education, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Students for the Craft Centre, 1990-1996 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Students for the Draft of President Nixon, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Students for the Non-Communist Unification of Greater Germany, 1986-1990 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Students for Thompson, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Students for Tom Loftus, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Students for Tom Schneider, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Students for Tuition Freeze, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Students for Union Reform (SURE), 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Students for USSA at UWM, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Students for WSUM, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Students Helping for Advocacy, Rehabilitation and Education, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Students in Solidarity Against Racism Coalition, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Students in Support of Women's Athletics at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Students International Mediation Society, 1970-1985 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Students Making a Responsible Tomorrow (SMART), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Students Making Improvements in Leadership and Education (SMILE), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Students Mobilized for Survival, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Students of Education, 1965-1972 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Students of Engineering and Applied Science, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Students Organize for Schmitz, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Students Organized Against Reagan (SOAR), 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Students Organized for Students, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Students Party, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Students' Rights Party, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Students Supporting Matt Flynn for Congress, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Students Taking a New Direction (S.T.A.), 1988 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Students to Encourage Patriotism, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Students to Support Milwaukee 14, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Students United for a Strong Stand in Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Students with a Disability (SWAD), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 118)